Thank you for watching!
Nogisaka no Chikyu
DONKASA DERBY
In Nogisaka, where there are many members who spill things or drop things
The final part of the competition to decide the most dongsa member in Nogisaka.
From the past episodes, the DONKUSUSA members of Erisuguri are competing against each other in various competitions.
They are competing against each other in various competitions.
Tonight, we'll start with the second half of the relay race, in which we only have to carry things.
Nakamura, what do you think of the battle so far?
When we were waiting for the set change
Teresa told Arno
I think it's a game that can be won if it's played right.
I lost, so the winner is the one who won.
Ikeda didn't just lose.
It was the only disqualification of the game.
Now let's move on to the baggage carriers
Tsutsui versus Endo.
Tsutsui, what do you think?
He seems to carry it slowly.
I'll be quick.
I see. Well, Endo, I've been told...
But he's taller than Ayame.
I think she's good at jumping over here.
I see.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Did you come up with something, Endo?
No, I didn't.
I just haven't heard what you have to say.
I'm sorry. Excuse me, sir.
Here we go.
Here it comes... one more time.
Tsutsui!
Otoshi rabio!
Ravio!
Oh, here he is!
Tsutsui was wearing a high mask.
He didn't know Ikeda's M.O. and chose the umbrella strategy.
It's going well.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
On the other hand, Endo's style is to go back and forth with the maximum amount he can carry steadily
Which one is faster?
Oh, that's good
Go, go, go!
Ok
Correct
Endo also kept a good pace, but
Tsutsui, who took the lead with the umbrellas all at once, continues to carry the load with no mistakes
We're going to lose if we don't keep up the pace.
Yes, sir.
We're going to lose.
You'd better hurry up.
There's only one more thing left.
I can't do it anymore.
It's too early.
I might slip, I might slip.
There it is. There it is.
Wow!
Oh, no, my legs are too tight.
Oh, there's enough left for all of this.
This is all the snacks.
Really?
You're late!
Endo, you're ahead of me.
Oh, no.
You don't have to carry them anymore.
That's right.
Why are you doing this?
That's why.
That was quick!
It was a winning strategy, wasn't it?
Yeah, there was plenty of time.
Well, Endo, if you were standing next to me, you'd have thought I was fast, right?
I thought he was fast.
You should've copied him.
I don't know... maybe it's because I want to keep the shape as it is.
I see.
I told you, you'd lose if you kept it like this.
That's right.
And you said, "That's right.
No, you didn't.
That's not true.
If Sameer's like this, he'll try his hardest not to lose.
Yes, we've been trying to figure out how to get there the fastest.
Don't take the blindfold off, if you haven't done it yet.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, sir.
That's one donkusapoint.
That's right.
I'll tell you what I'm giving you the blindfold for.
Next is Nakanishi vs. Kaki, who's running solo in Donksa
Nakanishi.
Yes, sir.
We just got the first place Donksa point.
Yes...
That's why we ran out of umbrellas.
I understand.
I'll make a plan and do my best.
What kind of strategy?
I don't have one yet.
I don't have one yet, but I will.
Kaki, you can't lose!
I don't think I can lose to Aru-no-chan
Here we go!
Here we go.
Come on, I want to cut down on the round trips.
But...
That was fast.
Here we go.
I'm so hungry.
You didn't bring anything.
Oh, man.
You're persistent.You're persistent.
While Kaki, who performed smoothly and quickly
while Nakanishi was slow in all his movements.
it's all right.
keep up the good work!
but
I can't do this.
Oh!
There it is.
Got it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yes. Yes.
You got it.
Vere.
You look like you want it.
I'm sorry.
True hollyhock.
Oh, no.
Why?
Stop it!
Five minutes.
Why?
Certainly.
Stop.
QUESTION
mainly
relative
redred
??
????
?
Pri
Because it's...
Coma.
It's okay.
Something's going to keep falling off forever.
What the fuck did you take your blindfold off for?
That's right.
Now, on to the next competition.
Mr. Hiblo, please.
Rap fast wrap.
You're not a very good rapper, are you, Donk Saisho?
Not very good.
The rules are simple.
All you have to do is wrap three plates.
You have to compete how fast you wrap them.
Put a layer of plastic wrap on a large pizza plate.
Oden is wrapped tightly so that the juice doesn't spill out.
The key is to wrap the cake gently so that it does not get crushed.
In addition
If there are any overflows, crumbles, or spills
Mr. Rimula will judge and tell you how many seconds
plus a few seconds.
So it's all about how fast and accurate you can be.
Lap race of unknown numbers
First, Inoue and Tsutsui face off.
Inoue Inoue.
It's easy, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
This doesn't mean that you have to wrap each pizza individually.
Think about when you put it away at home.
I understand.
What do you mean?
I'm 19.
Nineteen.
Okay, you two, let's go.
Here we go.
The first obstacle, finding the beginning of the rap, was finding the beginning of the rap.
Go for it!
You're fast!
Ahhh...
Oh no.
A little tough
Yes, yes, yes!
Inoue further extends his lead while Tsutsui can't start
But after the start, Tsutsui showed a furious pursuit
Inoue, who for some reason abandoned his case
And then, Inoue, who had abandoned his case, started to reinforce it with hand-torn wraps in a mysterious manner.
And then
Inoue, who also has a point of origin, lapped to the end.
Kimura checks the workmanship
Tsutsui first.
The cake has space here and here.
It's completely open here.
This is oden... it's a little sweet. This is oden, but it's a little sweet.
That's tough.
It's not safe if the soup comes out.
Here, here, here.
There's enough space for pizza.
There's a space here.
Tsutsui's record is 1 minute and 57 seconds after the starting point.
It's dirty.
This one is dirty too, so look, it's leaking, leaking, leaking...
This is dirty too!
Inoue was strictly checked.
No reversal, 3 tons of grass points!
Next, Endo vs. Kaki in a double center duel!
Now, Endo, do you play rap music?
I usually do.
I've never wrapped something this big before!
It's difficult.
Mr. Himura is the type of person who is very picky about wrapping.
There's a lot of space.
Do you look at the space?
We have to win.
I think we can win.
Sasaki is very dexterous.
Yes, he is.
Okay.
Come on, Yakubo, you already want Saki to win.
If you think you can wrap it up for me...
Maybe you can do it faster.
What do you mean, don't let me catch my breath?
I'm not. No, it's not.
I thought I'd give it to you as a present.
Yeah, well, I'll keep it for myself.
Okay, here we go... a quick wrap.
Here we go.
What a find!
It was Kaki who got out of the start of the wrap search.
I guess we're almost at the same start.
Ah!
It's so stupid!
Oh!
I'm a bit of a dunce
Ah!
Ah!that (something mentioned before which is distant psychologically or in terms of time)
that (something mentioned before which is distant psychologically or in terms of time)
Ah!
Yeah.
Kaki couldn't get a wrap after that.
Finished the cake in a ridiculous state and crossed the finish line
I wonder what would have happened if I had been home
And even in the judges' decision, Endo dominated and
This fight was 3 donksapoints to Kaki
Next, Ikeda vs. Nakanishi in the Donkusa summit battle
Nakanishi has to win now!
When I rap, even if there's an opening, I just put it in...When I wrap something, I just put it in even if it's empty.
What's the wrap for?
So air wouldn't get in there and it would dry out.
That's why it was rotten.
That's not why it was rotten.
Okay, here we go... the time trial.
Here we go.
The first one to reach the entrance of the lap is Nakanishi.
oh no... oh no... oh no... oh no...
But not the way he's holding it.
But Nakanishi was slow from the first lap.
He cut and pasted it once... and showed his laziness.
Ah, that method is so clumsy...
Ikeda couldn't find the entrance to the lap
and can't start at all!
Nakanishi, how long are you doing pizza?
Ikeda finally started the race, and he was catching up at a furious pace...
But it was Nakanishi who finished first!
Ikeda tried to make up for it with his politeness, but
But he could not make up for the too big delay.
Nakanishi was the winner in this duel.
Finally, Sato vs. Yoda in a showdown of sannsei donkusa!
Sato: How about the food at the beach?
But I've never been so particular about rapping.
I've never been that particular about rapping.
I think it's a part of my daily life.
How about you, Yoda? How about rapping?
I'm a rapper.
Yesterday, I had a little too much motsu nabe and dumplings.
I rapped.Wrap it up.
I'm doing it in Kinkin, so...
So you did rap yesterday at Kinkin?
In Sato sea
I'll erase it.
This morning.
This morning or this one is kumquat.
But I did a different rap yesterday.
You sang in the other rap?
Yakiniku rap.
What yakiniku rap?
In front of Den and Hazuki.
What's that?
It's a private thing.
You went out for yakiniku?
Yeah, we went out for yakiniku and you did a rap about it.
A different rap.
Can I hear that rap for a second?
No.
What kind of rap?
I don't know.
Unfortunately, the power of yakiniku goes hand in hand with the power of the sour.
Yakiniku is the best.
That's good.
Thank you for the rap before the rap battle.
I think it's good.
Okay, here we go.
All right, let's go.
I hate this.I hate this.
I don't know.
Wow, you're fast.
Uh, just now.
Not earlier.
I made the most of this confrontation with the Yoda rap, so I kept the main part of the show short.
Sato did a flurry of laps.
Here we go.
Here we go!
Yes, yes, yes.
Here we go.
Isn't this the fastest time you've ever had? I'm getting a little on the homey side.
What's so homey about it? This is open.
And Yoda's time was the best of the bunch, even though he was pointed out for his roughness.
Sato's performance was surprisingly well received, but Yoda's was no better.
Huh? Oh, well, it's coming out a little. It just came out a little.
I think, too, that Mr. Himura lifted it, lifted it, and spilled it.
Now...
The Donksa queens have finished the competition.
The winner of the first Donksa Queen is...
Nakanishi.
We did it! It was already decided.
But I've been thinking back. I used to work part-time at an Italian restaurant.
I got a lot of complaints because I really couldn't do my job.
That's funny.
What was that?What are you doing?
You're supposed to put the receipt in the customer's glass of water, not in the receipt jar.
Don't do it! And here we go! Nogizaka Construction Workshops! I'm your host, Bananaman, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you, Nogizaka-chan!
Here we go!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
dai dai dai dai dai dai dai dai dai dai dai dai dai dai
Seino
it's nice to meet you too
Kansai dialect
Kyoto dialect, I mean...
Well, I mean...
Why are you here today?
Kimura-san, please.
Thank you again this year, senpai.
Nogizaka Take-Care-of-Me Grand Prix
It's good, it's good, it's good, it's good, it's good.
Yay!
The Valentine's Day project, which has created many legends in the past, is back for this year's Okebitobo season!
This time, the youngest members will confess their feelings to their favorite senior members by giving them a caretaker's book as a token of their gratitude for their support this year.
However, the senior members who think they will be chosen will be asked to run for the position and confess their feelings for their favorite member.
They will be told that they will take care of you.
The best thing to do is to have a good relationship with your junior members.
The worst thing that can happen is that no one will be chosen.
It's not good.
If that happens, we'll have a drink to punish them.
What?
Punishment drinks for seniors?
That's right.
No, but let's have both.No, but let's do both.
So I want you to come out and say, "I can't let you drink it in the 5th period.
This time... yes... it's a punishment drink.
The program staff worked sleepless nights and nights to make it.
This year.
It's the strongest drink of the year.
The Ultimate Punishment Drink 2023 Final
Ultimate Punishment Drink 2023 Final!
We are preparing for it.
If it's the final, there's a possibility that it will be seriously poisoned.
And, of course, there will be people who won't get it.
Well, I've already warned you about this.
I won't cry.
I don't cry.
I don't know what it is, but I'm sure they're serious about it.
LOL!
Oh man, someone's definitely going to cry today.
I'm sure someone's going to cry today.
I can't believe they won't give me this... as a senior...
No, no, no, please don't say that.
You see, there are those who get it and those who don't. That's how it is. There are winners and losers.
That's what the grand prix is all about, so you can only pick one.
I'm going to confess who I've been indebted to first in the Grand Prix.
I'm sure it's the teenagers' place.
InoueI think I was especially indebted to my seniors during the live tour.
I'm sure you'll get it from Inoue.
They're all in contact with each other.
It's finally the start of the season, and it's going to be a rough year!
Raise your hands if you think you'll get Inoue's New Year's gift.
Now it's time for the curtain to rise!Now, it's time for the opening of the contest, so let's see who has raised their hands.
Here are the six who said they love Inoue. Now we'll ask them why they thought they could have me.
I have a frog, and when I tell people that I have a frog, they often say that they don't like it very much.
But Nagi-chan said she liked frogs, and I said I wanted to have a frog like this, and we had a lot of fun talking about frogs.
And it's not too thin?
No, no, no, no, there's more to it.
After the national tour, she said, "Thank you very much, Hazuki-san.
He said "thank you" to me after the tour?
We talked a lot during this tour, trying to get to know each other.
And he said thank you for extending the conversation. I see.
Well, well, well... I'm confident. But it's possible he only said that to Mukai.
I have a feeling that she doesn't like frogs. Is that her first topic of conversation?
Well, I don't know... just the two of us... something is bothering me...
Yes, we're good friends.
We often hang out when we're on tour... and go out to karaoke in private.
What?
We went out for dinner.
Really?
Oh, wow.
He's got a big private life.
This one looks strong.
Mukai, are you okay?
Wait, wait... I can't.
No, no, no. He might like frogs a lot.
That's right.
I don't know.
Are you guys going out for dinner or something?Are you going out for dinner or something?
Yes, ma'am.
You went a few times?
Heh.
What do they treat you to when you do? I don't know.
Well, yes, in a way.
That's great.
This looks pretty strong.
Yes, it is.
Yes, it looks strong.
Next, Endo.
Endo.
Why did you think you could get it?
Maybe because Nagi likes me.
I thought maybe you would give it to me.
It's true that in this project, it's because you've always been my favorite.
Yes, it's true that when you're doing this project, it's because you've always been a fan of Nagi's.
That's also a strong point, isn't it?
I see.
Even if you don't get anything, there is a pattern that you can get it.
That's why it's hard to tell.
I see.
It's always been...
Do you like the guy you like?
You don't have to say much. But do you always like him?
It's okay.
He's cute.
That's nice.
Go on, then. Kaki.Okay, then. Oysters.
Why did you think you'd get it?
It's not this year.
When Magi introduced me to Koichi Nogizaka for the first time...
So there's a pattern here.
We have similar interests.
We draw pictures together.
That's why I was the first to know Nagi-chan.
I see.
And we were standing next to each other on the tour.
Is that a big deal? Standing next to each other on the tour?
But I've seen that in the past when I've done this project.
I guess because we talk naturally.
So we're a little bit like friends?
I thought we were on the same page.
Why is it in the past tense?
I see what you mean. That's strong.
It's not Valentine's Day.
You're late.
It's more like "thank you" for your help.
It's difficult this time.
It's hard.
Why did you think you'd get it?
We're the only ones the same age.
The same age.
She's the only one who calls me Ayame-chan.
We went to graduation together.
You mean you went to school together?
That's pretty bold.
That's what I'm talking about.That's what I'm talking about.
We're on the same team.
Wow, that's possible.
Do any of the older students call you "chan"?
No, I call her Ayame.
I think we talk more casually.
I see.
Why did you come to Yumiki?
We were shooting a music video for "I Dream Twice.
Was there a song like that?
Please tell me.
When we were shooting the music video for "I Dream Twice"...
People dream twice.
Why do you sound like a preacher?
During the shooting of the music video
Nagi is a bit of a modest girl.
When she was sitting alone, if she thought I was alone
I would go up to her and talk to her.
I did that.
Nagi told me that she enjoys my company.
She told me I could talk to her without worrying about her.
I see.
She said she'd like to come to my house, too.
A girl like this doesn't ask to go to someone's house.
This kind of girl?
What kind of girl?
Not the type to say much the second time around.
I know, but she said it.
"I want to go to your house." That's a pretty big deal.It's pretty big to want to go home, isn't it?
Sounds big.
I don't know, Kimura-san.
It's hard, but after listening to the whole thing...
I don't think she wants to go home anymore.
I'm starting to feel that.
I thought I'd done a lot of work on the hall earlier.
If you've got the right person, clap, if not, sorry.
Who do you want to give your save to?
Who is it?
Is Inoue's true love here?
Yes!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy! Thank you!
Oh, my gosh, Yoda!
Sorry, something came up!
So Inoue gave a year-end gift he prepared for Yoda, who loves dumplings, to express his gratitude.
How did you do?
I really appreciate your help in this year's tour, and I've got a new massage therapist coming in for a new term.
Yoda-san went out of his way to create a group line for us,
I know it's hard to go to a massage when you have seniors there, but I know you are tired, so I hope you will go.
Wait a minute...there have been times in the past when you have created a group line, haven't there?
Didn't Akimoto go to a lot of trouble to make a group line for this kind of project?
No, really, I was talking with the physiologist about how the seniors were not looking good because they were getting massaged,
I thought it would be hard for them to go if someone didn't tell them, so I did it.
And they gave me a T-shirt.
Oh, T-shirts.
Yoda is into making T-shirts.
Yoda is really into making T-shirts these days. I felt like Yoda was amazing lately.
I told her I wanted one, and she said she made Nagi's too.
Is that so?
Yes, I did.
I was so happy when she gave it to me with her message on the day of the music video.
That's great that you took her out to dinner and so on. You are really doing something right, aren't you, senpai?
You are doing that kind of thing, Yoda.
No, I just felt like I had to pay back the senpai for all the things they had done for me.
Ah.
You could throw a party like that, couldn't you? Let's have it at our place.
I'd love to.
That sounds great.
Sorry, Yuki.
It's okay.
I wanted to go with you first.
No, you can't. No, you can't.
Please, those who lost, go back.
Please return.
Please don't learn from this and come back.
Please come back.
The product outline for the 34th single has been determined.
Tickets for Shinyama Mono live streaming and viewing are now on sale.
Hi, I'm Rika Sato.
I've been working hard on stage recently.
I will do my best on stage and in Nogichu with this twintail Wadagaki-chan hair.
Please subscribe to my channel.